We're moving on to the next step in our quick Thai curry.
Now we've got our vegetables ready to go that we've talked about.
We're firing up our wok.
A little bit of oil on the bottom of the wok.
Get that hot and ready to go.
The first thing you want to add to your wok are your fresh vegetables.
If you're using frozen vegetables, you want to take those out of their package, let them defrost for a couple of minutes.
If you're mixing fresh and frozen, you definitely want to get your frozen vegetables out so they're maybe up to almost room temperature so that everything is going to cook at the same pace.
When we're cooking with a wok and cooking Thai food, your vegetables are going to be crispy.
They're not going to be overdone.
So everything that we're going to cook today is cooked very quickly.
This is not a long cooking process that we're going to be doing.
Looks like our wok is ready to go.
The first thing we're going to do is add at least one or two cloves of garlic.
Get that in and get that going.
That's a nice base flavor for anything that we're going to be cooking today.
And then the next thing we're going to add are our heavier vegetables, like our carrot, our onion and today we're using peppers.
So let's get our peppers in there.
You want to make sure that your vegetables are in.
Toss your vegetables around.
Okay.
There's our vegetables.
We're stirring them, keeping them moving so that they cook evenly in the wok.
It's important that you do keep them moving so that you don't end up with your vegetables cooked unevenly.
If you were cooking with broccoli or another harder vegetable like that, you'd also want those in at this time.
Just keep moving that around.
You can leave it periodically.
Let the vegetables heat up and in about thirty seconds or so come on back, keep it moving again.
In a minute we'll be back and talk about the next step in our dinner.